let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Will I get this question right?",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Maybe",
      "I don't know"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What about this one?",
    answer: "No",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Maybe",
      "I don't know"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How about this?",
    answer: "Maybe",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Maybe",
      "I don't know"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Or this?",
    answer: "I don't know",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Maybe",
      "I don't know"
    ]
  },
//     {
//     numb: 5,
//     question: "What colour Christmas is Elvis going to have?",
//     answer: "Blue",
//     options: [
//       "White",
//       "Red",
//       "Blue",
//       "Green"
//     ]
//   },
//     {
//     numb: 6,
//     question: "Which Hollywood actor played six different roles in The Polar Express?",
//     answer: "Tom Hanks",
//     options: [
//       "Tom Hanks",
//       "Richard Attenborough",
//       "Tim Allen",
//       "Bruce Willis"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 7,
//     question: "What are you supposed to do when you find yourself under the mistletoe?",
//     answer: "Kiss",
//     options: [
//       "Dance",
//       "Sing",
//       "Kiss",
//       "Run away"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 8,
//     question: "Which real-life person is Santa Claus based on?",
//     answer: "St. Nicholas",
//     options: [
//       "St. Christopher",
//       "St. Bernard",
//       "St. Jude",
//       "St. Nicholas"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 9,
//     question: "In the movie Elf, what was the first rule of The Code of Elves?",
//     answer: "Treat everyday like Christmas",
//     options: [
//       "Treat everyday like Christmas",
//       "Check the list twice",
//       "There is room for everyone on the nice list",
//       "The BEST way to spread Christmas cheer is singing loud for all to hear"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 10,
//     question: "How do you say Merry Christmas in Spanish?",
//     answer: "Feliz Navidad",
//     options: [
//       "Nollaig Shona",
//       "Feliz Navidad",
//       "Marau na Kerisimasi",
//       "Meri Kirihimete"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 11,
//     question: "What is the best-selling Christmas song ever?",
//     answer: "White Christmas by Bing Crosby",
//     options: [
//       "All I Want for Christmas Is You by Mariah Carey",
//       "Do They Know It's Christmas by Band Aid",
//       "Fairytale of New York by The Pogues",
//       "White Christmas by Bing Crosby"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 12,
//     question: "What was Frosty the Snowman's nose made out?",
//     answer: "A button",
//     options: [
//       "Corn cob pipe",
//       "A button",
//       "Coal",
//       "A carrot"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 13,
//     question: "What popular Christmas song was actually written for Thanksgiving?",
//     answer: "Jingle Bells",
//     options: [
//       "Jingle Bells",
//       "Deck the Halls",
//       "Joy to the World",
//       "O Holy Night"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 14,
//     question: "What was the first company that used Santa Claus in advertising?",
//     answer: "Coca Cola",
//     options: [
//       "Pepsi",
//       "Dr. Pepper",
//       "Coca Cola",
//       "Mountain Dew"
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     numb: 15,
//     question: "What is The Grinches dog's name?",
//     answer: "Max",
//     options: [
//       "Fido",
//       "Charlie",
//       "Buddy",
//       "Max"
//     ]
//   },
];